So the first one here is this glaring typo in the given name column for David Gustafsson.
لذا، فإن الأمر الأول هنا يتمثل في هذا الخطأ المطبعي الصارخ في عمود الاسم المعطى لـ David Gustafsson.
David spelled D s v i d. As you can see in the contact column here his email has David,
تهجئة David  "D s vi i d". كما ترون في عمود الاتصال هنا بريده الإلكتروني مكتوب فيه David،
so this is definitely a typo.
إذن، فإن هذا بالتأكيد خطأ مطبعي.
So how could this have happened?
ولكن كيف حدث هذا؟
This is probably just another data entry error.
ربما هذا مجرد خطأ آخر في إدخال البيانات.
And, why is it important to fix this?
ولماذا من المهم إصلاح هذا؟
Well, if you want to email or send mail to this person,
حسنًا، إذا كنت تريد مراسلة هذا الشخص إلكترونيًا أو ترسل إليه بريدًا،
if you misspelled their name that's not very nice for David here.
وأخطأت في كتابة اسمه فلن يكون الأمر لطيفًا جدًا بالنسبة إلى David هنا.
Again, that's if you're just sending email in
مرة أخرى ، هذا إذا كنت فقط ترسل بريدًا إلكترونيًا
an automated fashion by picking at this name from this patient's table.
بطريقة آلية عن طريق اختيار هذا الاسم من جدول المريض.
So, time to document it.
لذا ، حان الوقت لتوثيقها.
These treatments and patients table are starting to pile up here.
تبدأ هذه العلاجات وجدول المرضى تتراكم هنا.
So, let's separate these into sub-headers again.
لذا، دعنا نفصلها إلى عناوين فرعية مرة أخرى.
This data wrangling template can be adjusted as you see fit here.
يمكن تعديل قالب تعارض البيانات هذا حسب ما تراه مناسبًا هنا.
It's not a rigid document.
إنها ليست وثيقة ثابتة.
Tweak it to your own personal preferences.
اضبطه على تفضيلاتك الشخصية.
So, the next issue is in the treatment table here.
لذا، فإن المشكلة التالية في جدول العلاج هنا.
Specifically, the auralin and novodra columns.
على وجه التحديد، أعمدة auralin وnovodra.
There are a few issues with this column but let's dial in on one right now.
هناك بعض المشكلات في هذا العمود، ولكن دعنا نبحث عنها الآن.
The fact that these dosages are documented in digit, digit, u form.
في حقيقة، يتم توثيق هذه الجرعات بالأرقام، شكل u
So, for the first patient in this table,
لذلك ، بالنسبة لأول مريض في هذا الجدول،
the starting dose of auralin was 41 units and the ending dose was 48 units.
كانت جرعة البداية من auralin 41 وحدة وبلغت جرعة النهاية 48 وحدة.
These should actually be in separate columns but we'll handle that later.
يجب أن تكون هذه الجرعات في الواقع في أعمدة منفصلة، ولكن سنقوم بمعالجتها لاحقًا.
The fact that there's the letter u here attached to the end means that
حقيقة أن وجود حرف u هنا مرفق في النهاية يعني أن
Pandas would not be able to interpret this variable as a float or an integer,
Pandas لن تتمكن من تفسير هذا المتغير على أنه عائم أو عدد صحيح،
which is required for calculations.
وهو مطلوب لإجراء الحسابات.
Because the letter u is there Pandas would force it to the data type object.
بسبب وجود حرف u، ستجبرها Pandas على كائن نوع البيانات.
Which is basically a string in Pandas.
وهو في الأساس سلسلة في Pandas.
That means we can't perform calculations
وهذا يعني أننا لا نستطيع إجراء العمليات الحسابية
using the starting and ending doses for each drug.
باستخدام جرعات البداية والنهاية لكل عقار.
That's a big deal. So, how could this issue have happened?
هذا الأمر مهم. إذن، كيف حدث هذا الأمر؟
Sometimes it's just poor planning on behalf of whoever's recording this information,
في بعض الأحيان يكون التخطيط ضعيفًا من جانب عن الشخص الذي يسجل هذه المعلومات،
this clinical trial result data.
هذه البيانات نتيجة التجارب السريرية.
Say if the person who was recording
لو قيل إن الشخص الذي كان يسجل
this information was writing it down in a piece of paper.
هذه المعلومات كان يقوم بكتابتها في ورقة،
Maybe they weren't aware that the data would be transferred from paper
فلربما لم يكن على دراية بأن البيانات سيتم نقلها من الورق
to computer using something like optical character recognition,
إلى الكمبيوتر باستخدام شيء مثل التعرّف البصري على الحروف،
which would pick up these Us and dashes here,
والذي سيلتقط هذه Us والشرطات هنا،
rather than simply the integer that we want.
بدلاً من مجرد العدد الصحيح الذي نريده.
So, let's document this now. This is a big one to fix.
لذا، دعنا نوثق هذا الآن. هذا خطأ كبير ينبغي إصلاحه.
And here's how the observation could be written.
ويهذا نعرف كيف يمكن كتابة الملاحظة.
All right, so backup to the treatment's table.
حسنًا، لذا ينبغي أخذ نسخة احتياطية لجدول العلاج.
One other issue is that these given names and
هناك مشكلة أخرى تتمثل في أن هذه الأسماء
surnames in the treatment's table are all lowercase.
والألقاب المذكورة في جدول العلاجات بحروف صغيرة.
Actually same goes for the adverse_reactions table.
في الواقع، ينطبق الأمر نفسه على جدول التفاعلات الضارة.
This is an issue because the patients table is not lowercase.
هذه مشكلة لأن جدول المرضى ليس مكتوبًا بحروف صغيرة.
This becomes an issue if you want to join these tables later.
ويصبح هذا مشكلة إذا كنت ترغب في ضم هذه الجداول معًا فيما بعد.
Which I hint for later, I think we want to.
ما ألمح إليه بقول "فيما بعد"، أعتقد أننا نريد ذلك.
This is probably a data recording or data entry error issue,
ربما تكون هذه مشكلة في تسجيل أو إدخال البيانات،
and we'll document this with observations.
وسنقوم بتوثيقها باستخدام الملاحظات.
One for the treatment's table and one for the adverse_table.
واحدة لجدول العلاجات والأخرى لجدول التفاعلات الضارة.
And, for the final one let's scroll to the bottom of the treatment's table.
وبالنسبة للجزء الأخير، دعنا ننتقل إلى أسفل جدول العلاجات.
There are 280 rows,
هناك 280 صفًا،
with last index being 279 because there's zero index to this data frame.
مع كون المؤشر الأخير 279 لأن هناك مؤشر صفري لإطار البيانات هذا.
So, if you recall the size of each treatment arm was actually 175 patients in each.
لذا، إذا كنت تتذكر حجم جميع أذرع العلاجات، كان في الواقع 175 مريضا في كل منهما.
175 for the auralin arm and 175 for the novodra arm.
175 لذراع  auralin و 175 لذراع novodra.
So, it looks like we're missing some data here.
لذلك، يبدو أننا نفقد بعض البيانات هنا.
Finding where that data lives is a separate issue.
إن العثور على مكان وجود البيانات يمثل مشكلة منفصلة.
But we'll deal with that later.
لكننا سنتعامل مع ذلك لاحقًا.
And for now we'll just document this with an observation.
وفي الوقت الحالي، سنوثق هذا بملاحظة.
We should have 350 total.
يجب أن يكون لدينا إجمالي قدره 350.
175 times-
175 مرة-